manual: adj. 体力的
Lesson 4. The Double Life of Alfred Blogs. These days, people who do manual work often receive
第4课。阿尔弗雷德博客的双重生活。这些天，从事手动工作的人经常接受
far more money than people who work in offices. People who work in offices are frequently referred
比在办公室工作的人要多得多。在办公室工作的人经常被推荐
collar: n.  衣领
to as white collar workers for the simple. Reason that they usually wear a collar and tie to go to work.
作为简单的白领工人。他们通常会戴领并领带上班的原因。
sacrifice: v.  牺牲，献出
Such as human nature, that a great many people are often willing to sacrifice higher pay for
例如人性，很多人通常愿意为更高的薪水牺牲
collar: n.  衣领, privilege: n.  好处
the privilege of becoming. White collar workers. This can give rise to curious situations. As it
成为的特权。白领工人。这可能会引起奇怪的情况。这样
dustman: n.  清洁工
did in the case of Alfred Blogs who worked as a dustman for the Elsemier Corporation.
以阿尔弗雷德（Alfred）博客为例，他曾在埃尔西米尔公司（Elsemier Corporation）担任尘埃落定。
When he got married, Alf was too embarrassed to say anything to his wife about his job.
当他结婚时，阿尔夫（Alf）太尴尬了，无法对他的妻子对他的工作说什么。
He simply told her that he worked for the Corporation. Every morning, he left home dressed in a
他只是告诉她他在公司工作。每天早晨，他都穿着
dustman: n.  清洁工, overalls: n.  工作服
smart black suit. He then changed into overalls and spent the next eight hours as a dustman.
聪明的黑色西装。然后，他变成了工作服，并在接下来的八个小时里担任尘土飞扬的人。
shower: n.  淋浴
Before returning home at night, he took a shower and changed back into his suit. Alf did this
在晚上返回家园之前，他洗了个澡，换上了他的西装。阿尔夫这样做了
dustman: n.  清洁工, secret: n.  秘密
for over two years and his fellow dustman kept his secret Alf's wife has never.
两年多来，他的尘土飞扬的同胞一直保持他的秘密ALF的妻子从来没有。
dustman: n.  清洁工
Discovered that she married a dustman and she never will. For Alf has just found another job.
发现她嫁给了尘土飞扬的人，她永远不会。因为阿尔夫刚刚找到了另一份工作。
He will soon be working in an office. He will be earning only half as much as he used to.
他很快将在办公室工作。他的赚取只会像以前那样的一半。
status: n.  地位
But he feels that his rise in status is well worth the loss of money. From now on, he will wear a suit
但是他认为自己的地位上升非常值得损失金钱。从现在开始，他会穿西装
all day and others will call him Mr. Blogs. Not Alf.
整天，其他人会称他为博客先生。不是alf。